Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- User Groups & Newsletters, Series 12
  - Applesauce [L.A./Chino] Vol. 2 No. 1 - 5, 1980 Oct. - 1981 July (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Apple Shine [Miami] Vol. 2 No. 8; Vol. 3 No. 1, 3, 4, 1985 Oct. - 1986 July (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Apple Shine [Miami], 1987 Apr. - 1989 Apr. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Apple Skinner News [Eugene] Vol. 2 No. 4; Vol. 3 No. 2, 4 - 9, 11, 1983 Apr. - 1984 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Apple Tree Computer Club [Chicago], 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Apple Tree Computer Club [Chicago], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Apple Tree Computer Club [Chicago], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Apple Tree Computer News, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Apple Tree Computer News, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Apple Tree Computer Club News, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Apple Tree Computer Club News, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Apple Van [Vancouver WA] Vol. 9 No. 3 - 6, 9, 10, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 3, 1989 Sept. - Dec. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    not reqional
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 4 No. 4 - 7; Vol. 5, No. 2, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    not regional
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 5 No. 4, 6, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 5, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    [Disk] not regional
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 6 No. 3; Vol. 7 No. 1, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Apple Works [The AppleWorks Educator] Vol. 7 No. 1, 1992 Sept. - Oct. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    not regional [disk]
  - Apple Works Journal [ALUG] Vol. 1 No. 1 - 3, 7 - 9, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Apple Works Journal [ALUG] Vol. 1 No. 10 - 12 & Reference, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - BETA Macs News [Henderson TX] Vol. 2 No. 5, 6, 8, 9, 12; Vol. 3 No. 1, 5, 1986 - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bits and Bytes Vol. 2 No. 10; Vol. 1 No. 11, 1986 - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA], 1985 Spring (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA], 1985 Fall (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA], 1986 Spring (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA], 1986 LATE (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA], 1987 Fall / Winter (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA] Vol. 4 No. 2, 1988 Summer / Fall (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - BMUG Newsletter [Berkeley CA] Vol. 5 No. 2, 1989 Summer / Fall (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - BMUG Membership / Order Forms, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - BMUG Membership Offer, 1997 June (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - BMUG Membership Newsletter, 1998 July - Aug. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Call Apple Vol. 1 No. 8, 1978 Sept. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Call Apple Vol. 2 No. 1, 1979 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Call Apple Vol. 2 No. 2, 1979 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Call Apple Vol. 2 No. 3, 4, 1979 Mar. - May (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Call Apple, 1979 Sept. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Call Apple, 1979 Oct. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Call Apple, 1979 Nov. - Dec. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Call Apple Vol. 3 No. 1 - 5, 1980 Jan. - June (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Call Apple Vol. 3 No. 6 - 9, 1980 July - Dec. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Call Apple Vol. 4 No. 1 -5, 1981 Jan. - June (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Call Apple Vol. 4 No. 6 - 9, 1981 July - Dec. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Call Apple Vol. 5 No. 1 - 6, 1982 Jan. - June (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Call Apple Vol. 5 No. 7 - 12, 1982 July - Dec. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Call Apple Vol. 6 No. 1 - 4, 1983 Jan. - Apr. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Call Apple Vol. 6 No. 5 - 8, 1983 May (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Call Apple Vol. 6 No. 9 - 11, 1983 Sept. - Dec. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Call Apple Vol. 7 No. 1 - 4, 1984 Jan. - Apr. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Call Apple Vol.7 No. 5 - 7, 1984 May - July (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Call Apple Vol. 7 No. 8 - 11, 1984 Aug. - Dec. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Call Apple Vol. 8 No. 1 - 6, 1985 Jan. - June (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Call Apple Vol. 8 No. 7 - 9, 11, 12, 1985 July - Dec. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Call Apple Vol. 9 No. 1 - 4, 1986 Jan. - Apr. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Call Apple Vol. 9 No. 6 - 12, 1986 June - Dec. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Call Apple Vol. 10 No. 1 - 6, 1987 Jan. - June (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Call Apple [Renton WA], 1987 July - Dec. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Call Apple [Renton WA], 1988 Jan. - June (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Call Apple [Renton WA], 1988 July - Dec. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Call Apple [Renton WA], 1989 Jan. -May (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Charlotte [NC] Apple News Letter, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - CIA Informer [Peoria IL], 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cider Press Vol. 2 No. 6, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cider Press [Best of 1978 - 1979] (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cider Press, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cider Press [Best of 1980] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1983 Dec./1984 Jan. - Dec. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Cider Press [SF CA], 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Club Apple Newsletter [France]: L'echo des Apple, 1985 June. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Club Mac News Vol. 1 No. 1 - 3, 5 - 7, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Club Mac News Vol. 11 No. 8 - 11, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Club Mac Road Show [Boulder CO], 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - CMC News [Computers and The Media Center] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 3, 1981 - 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - CMC News [Computers and The Media Center] Vol. 6 No. 1; Vol. 7, No. 1 - 4; Vol. 8 No. 2 - 3; Vol. 9, No. 2 - 4, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Command Drexel U. [ Philadelphia PA], Winter 87/88 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cupertino Mac Club Materials, Cupertino, Italy, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Desert Dialogue [Las Vegas NV] Vol. 83 - 85, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Desert Dialogue [Las Vegas NV] Vol. 7 No. 2 - 4, Vol. 8 No. 5, Vol. 7 No. 6, 10 - 12, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Desk Top Journal Vol. 1 No. 2 - 3, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Desk Top Journal Vol. 1 No. 4 - 5; Vol. 2 No. 1, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Desk Top Journal Vol. 2 No. 2 Issue 10, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The Desk Top Journal Issue 12, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - EBMUG [Newsletter Pinole CA], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Empire Macintosh News and Views [ Yucaipa CA] Vol. 1 No. 11, 14, 17, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Forum Vol. 1 No. 1 - 5, 1986 Aug. - Dec. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Forum Vol. ..2 No. 1 - 2, 4 - 9, 1987 Jan. - Sept. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Forum Vol. 2 No. 10 - 12, 1987 Oct. - Dec. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Forum Vol. 3 No. 1 - 3, 5 - 7, 1988 Jan. - July. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Forum Vol. .3 No. 8 - 12, 1988 Aug. - Dec. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Forum Vol. 4 No. 1 - 4, 6 - 7, 1989 Jan. - July. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Forum Vol. 4 No. 9 - 12, 1989 Sept. - Dec. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Forum Vol. 5 No. 1 - 4, 1990 Jan. - Apr. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Forum Vol. 5 No. 5 - 8, 1990 May - Aug. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Forum Vol. 5 No. 9 - 12, 1990 Sept. - Dec. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Forum Vol. 6 No. 1 - 4, 1991 Jan. - Apr. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Forum Vol. 6 No. 5 - 8, 1991 May. - Aug. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Forum Vol. 6 No. 9 -12, 1991 Sept. - Dec. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Forum Vol. 7 No. 1 - 3, 1992 Jan. - Mar. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Forum Vol. 7 No. 4 - 7, 1992 Apr. - July (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Forum Vol. 7 No.8 - 12, 1992 Aug. - Dec. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Forum Vol. 10 No. 5 - 10, 1995 May - Dec. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - GAB'er [Guilder Land NY] Vol. 9 No. 11, 1993 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gravenstein [Petaluma CA], 1995 May (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Happy Apple Press [North San Diego] No. 29 - 33, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Happy Apple Press [North San Diego] No. 34, 36, 41, 43 - 44, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Happy Apple Press [North San Diego] No. 46 - 57, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Happy Apple Press [North San Diego] No. 58 - 60, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Hard Core [England] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 3, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 6 No. 6 - 8, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 8 No. 1 - 2, 4 - 5, 1986 Jan. - May (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 8 No. 6 - 9, 1986 June - Sept. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 8 No. 10 - 11, 1986 Oct. - Nov. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 9 No. 1 - 4, 1986 Dec. / 1987 Jan. - June / July (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 9 No. 5 - 7; Vol. 10 No. 8; Vol. 9 No. 9, 1986 Dec. / 1987 Jan. - June / July (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 10 No. 1 - 5, 1988 Jan. - May (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 10 No. 6 - 7, 10 - 11, 1988 June - Nov. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 11 No. 12; Vol. 12 No. 1; Vol. 11 No. 10 - 11, 1988 Dec. / 1989 Jan. - Nov. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 12 No. 1 - 5, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Harvest [Arlington Heights IL] Vol. 13 No. 2, 4, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Historically Brewed: Historical Computer Soeiety [El Paso TX] Issue # 1, 1993 Aug. / Sept. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Icon [A32 Users] Vol. 8 No. 3; Vol. 9 No. 1, 1991 - 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Icon [A32 Users] Vol. 12 No. 3, 1995 - 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Inside Apple [Charlotte NC], 1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Inside Apple [Charlotte NC], 1985 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Inside Apple [Charlotte NC], 1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Inside Apple [Charlotte NC], 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Intelligencer: The Mac Intelligencer [Mensa SIG] Vol. 1 No. 4 - 6, 9 - 10; Vol. 2 No. 11 - 12, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Intelligent Vol. 3 No. 1 - 6, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Intelligent: The Intelligent Mac [Mensa SIG] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 12, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Intelligent: The Intelligent Mac [Mensa SIG] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 2; Vol. 5 No. 2, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK] Vol. 6 No. 9 - 11, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK] Vol. 7 No. 1, 3, 7 - 12, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK] Vol. 8 No. 1 - 5, 12, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK] Vol. 9 No. 1 - 9, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK] Vol. 10 No. 1 - 2, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1986 Jan. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - I / O Port Tulsa Computer Society Phone Book [Tulsa OK], 1986 Dec. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1987 Jan. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1988 Jan. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1989 Jan. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1990 Jan. - June (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1991 Sept. - Nov. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - I / O Port [Tulsa OK], 1992 Jan. - Oct. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - I / O Port Newsletter Tulsa Computer Society [Tulsa OK], 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Kalamazoo Apple Computer User's Society Newsletter [Kalamazoo MI]Vol. 9 No. 6, 1998 June (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - KAUG NewsBytes [Kokomo], 1995 June (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Lisa Lives [Palm Beach Gardens FL], 1994 Spring (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The Lisa Talk Report Vol. 2 No. 1 - 3, 1986 Spring, Summer, Fall (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Little Rock Apple Addicts [AR] Vol. 3 No. 3, 4, 6, 1981 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Little Rock Apple Addicts [AR] Vol. 6 No. 1 - 9, 11, 1984 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Little Rock Apple Addicts [AR] Vol. 7 No. 1, 3 - 11, 1985 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Little Rock Apple Addicts [AR] Vol. 8 No. 1 - 6, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mac Classifieds Vol. 2 No. 1 - 5, 1986 - 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - MacCountry News [Santa Rosa CA], 1995 - 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 1 No. 3 - 5, 1984 Oct. - Dec. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 2 No. 1, 3; Vol. 3 No. 1 - 2, 1985 Jan. - Feb. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 4 No. 1, 4, 7 - 12, 1986 Jan. - Dec. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 5 No. 1, 2, 4 - 8, 1987 Jan. - Aug. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 5 No. 9 - 12, 1987 Sept. - Dec. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 6 No. 2, 3, 5 - 7, 9, 1988 Feb. - 1988 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 6 No. 10, 11, 1988 Oct. - Nov. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 7 No. 1, 4 - 6, 1989 Jan. - Sept. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 7 No. 11, 12, 1989 Nov. - Dec. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 8 No. 2 - 5, 1990 Feb. - May (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 8 No. 7; Vol. 9 No. 8, 1990 July - Aug. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 9 No. 3, 8, 11, 12, 1991 Mar. - Dec. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - MacDigest [L.A. CA] Vol. 10 No. 1 - 4, 1992 Jan. - Apr. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mac FUG News [University of UT, SLU UT] Vol. 2 No. 9; Vol. 3 No. 0 - 4, 1986 June - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Mac FUG News [University of UT, SLU UT]Vol. 3 No. 5 - 11; Vol. 4 No. 1 - 4, 1987 Jan - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Mac FUG News [University of UT, SLU UT]Vol. 4 No. 5 - 12; Vol. 5 No. 1, 2, 1988 Jan. - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - MacGate [Colgate U. Hamilton NY]Vol. 1 No. 2, 3, 1985 Dec. - 1986 Mar. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Mac Mania [Corona CA] Vol. 4 No. 5, 6, 8 - 12; Vol. 5 No. 2 - 6, 8, 9, 1986 June - 1988 Oct. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 2 No. 6, 9 - 12, 1986 June - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 6, 9 - 12, 1987 Jan. - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 12, 1988 Jan. - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 5 No. 1 - 5, 7, 1989 Jan. - July (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 5 No. 8 - 12, 1989 Aug. - Dec. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 6 No. 1 - 5, 1990 Jan. - May (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 6 No. 6, 9 - 12, 1990 June - Dec. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 7 No. 1 - 3, 5, 8, 9, 1991 Jan. - Sept. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Mac News [Eugene OR] Vol. 8 No. 2, 4, 1992 Feb. - Apr. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Mac News Update [Eugene OR] Vol. 3 - 6, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - MacNexus Vol. 1 No. 4 - 12, 1985 Jan. - Dec. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - MacNexus Vol. 2 No. 1 - 12, 1986 Jan. - Dec. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - MacNexus Vol. 2 No. 3 - 9, 1987 Jan. - Sept. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - MacNexus Vol. 2 No. 11, 15, 1987 Nov. - Dec. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - MacNexus Vol. 1.08C, 1.13D, 1.16D, 1.17D, 1988 Mar. - Dec. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - MacNexus Vol. 2.0A, 2.2A, 2.3A, 1989 Feb. - Apr. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - MacNuggets [Carmegie-Mellon U. Pittsburgh PA] Vol. 2, No. 1, 1986 Apr. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Mac Page [Kalamzzon MI], 1988 Mar. - June (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 4 No. 1, 2, 1986 Sept. - Nov. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 4 No. 3, 5 - 9, 1986 Dec. - 1987 Aug. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 4 No. 9, 11 - 13, 1987 Sept. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 5 No. 1, 2, 4 - 6, 1988 Jan. - June (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 5 No. 7 - 9, 12, 1988 July - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 6 No. 1 - 5, 1989 Jan. - May (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 6 No. 6, 9, 10, 1989 June - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 7 No. 1, 2, 5, 1990 Jan. - June (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 8, No. 2 - 5, 1991 Apr. - May (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - The Mac Street Journal [NYC] Vol. 8, No. 9, 12, 1991 Sept. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 3 No. 8, 10 - 12, 1988 Aug. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 5 No. 1, 3 - 5, 10 - 12, 1990 Jan. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 6 No. 2 - 12, 1991 Feb. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 7 No. 1 - 4, 9 - 12; Vol. 10 No. 1, 6 - 8, 1992 Jan. - Dec. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 4 No. 1- 7, 9 - 11, 1989 Jan. - Nov. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Mac Yak News [Yakima WA] Vol. 10 No. 5 - 9, 11 - 12; Vol. 11 No. 1- 4, 1995 May - 1996 Apr. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - MacinTalk [Nashville TN], 1989 Mar. - Dec. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - MacinTalk [Nashville TN], 1990 Jan. - Dec. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - MacinTalk [Nashville TN], 1991 Jan. - Aug. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - MacinTalk [Nashville TN], 1991 Sept. - 1992 June (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - MacinTalk [Nashville TN], 1995 Sept. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Macintosh Connection Vol. 1 No. 5 - 8, 1985 Jan. - June (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Macintosh Lab Monitor Vol. 1 - 4, 1986 Fall - 1987 Summer (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - MacInTouch, 1985 Nov. - 1986 Feb. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - MacInTouch, 1986 Mar. - Dec. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - MacInTouch, 1987 Jan. - Apr. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The MACNJ Window Vol. 9 No. 1, 1995 Jan. - Aug. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - MACs of Marin [SRafael CA] Vol. 1 No. 2 - 6; Vol. 2 No. 7, 1987 July - 1988 June (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - MACs of Marin [SRafael CA] Vol. 3 No. 13 - 16, 1989 May - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - MACs of Marin [SRafael CA] Vol. 3 No. 17, 18; Vol. 4 No. 19; Vol. 5 No. 25, 29, 30, 1990 Mar. - 1992 Apr. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Mac Tech Source Vol. 1 No. 1, 2, 1984 Sept. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Mac Useful [N.O. LA] Vol. 1 No. 2 - 4, 1986 Oct. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mac Useful [N.O. LA] Vol. 2 No. 5, 1987 Mar. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Mac Useful [N.O. LA], 1988 Aug. - Nov. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 2 No. 1, 5 - 11, 1986 May - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 10, 12, 1987 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 3, 5 - 8, 10 - 12, 1988 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 5 No. 1, 2, 4, 5, 9 - 12, 1989 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 6 No. 1 - 6, 8 - 12, 1990 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 7 No. 1 - 3, 7, 9, 10, 1991 Jan. - Oct. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mac Valley Voice [ Burbank CA] Vol. 8 No. 1 - 3, 10, 11, 1992 Jan. - Nov. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 1 No. 1,4 - 7, 10, 12, 1986 Mar. - Dec. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 2 No. 1 - 3, 5, 10 - 12, 1987 Jan. - Dec. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 3 No. 1 - 8, 1988 Jan. - Aug. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 3 No. 9 - 10, 12, 1988 Sept. - Dec. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 4, 1989 Jan. - May. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 4 No. 6 - 8, 10 - 12, 1989 June - Dec. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 5 No. 1 - 5, 1990 Jan - May (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 5 No. 7 - 11, 1990 July - Nov. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 5 - 6 No. 12 / 1 - 3, 5, 1990 Dec.-1991 May (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 6 No. 6 / 7, 10 / 11, 1991 July - Nov. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 7 No. 2, 1992 Fed. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Mad Mac News [Madison WI] Vol. 10 No. 7, 1995 Aug. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - The Main Menu [Apple Works] Vol. 1 No. 1 - 3, 1986 Oct. - Dec. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Mar - Creek Apple II [MAMC Newsletter Kalamazoo MI], 1987 Jan. Mar. May (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 4 No. 2 - 4, 9 - 12, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 5 No. 1 - 7, 1982 Jan - July (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 5 No. 9 - 12, 1982 Oct. - Dec. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 6 No. 1, 3 - 6, 1983 Jan. - June. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 6 No. 11 - 12, 1983 Sept. - Dec. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 7 No. 1 - 5, 1984 Jan. - May. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 7 No. 6 - 10, 1984 June - Oct. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 7 No. 11 - 12, 1984 Nov. - Dec. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 8 No. 1 - 5, 1985 Jan. - May. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 8 No. 6 - 8, 10 - 12, 1985 June - Dec. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 9 No. 1 - 4, 1986 Jan. - Apr. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 9 No. 5 - 8, 10 - 11, 1986 May- Nov. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 10 No. 1 - 5, 1987 Jan - May (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 10 No. 6 - 12, 1987 June - Dec. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 11 No. 2 - 4, 7 - 8, 10 - 12, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 12 No. 1 - 4, 6 - 8, 10, 12, 1989 Jan. - Dec. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 13 No. 1 - 5, 1990 Jan.. - May (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 13 No. 6 - 10, 1990 June - Oct. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 14 No. 1 - 2, 4 - 6, 8, 10, 1991 Jan. - Dec. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 15 No. 1, 1992 Jan. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mini'app'les [MN] Vol. 18 No. 9 - 11, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 3 No. 5 - 7, 9, 11 - 12, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 4 No. 1 - 3, 7 - 8, 1987 Jan. - Aug. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 4 No. 10 - 12, 1987 Oct. - Dec. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 5 No. 1, 3 - 4, 6 - 8, 1988 Jan. - Aug. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 5 No. 10 - 12, 1988 Oct. - Dec. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Mouse Droppings Vol. 6 No. 1 - 6, 8, 1989 Jan. - Aug. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1989 Sept. - Dec. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1990 Jan. - June (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1990 July - Dec. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1991 Jan. - May (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1991 June - Aug. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Mouse Droppings, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - The Mouseketeer Vol. 1 No. 12; Vol. 2 No. 1 or 2, 3, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 2 No. 2, 4 - 7, 1986 Fed - July. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 2 No. 8, 10, 1986 Aug. - Oct. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 4 No. 3 - 4, 6 - 7, 1988 May - July (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 4 No. 8 - 9, 1988 Aug. - Oct. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 5 No. 1 - 4, 1989 Jan. - Apr. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 5 No. 5 - 6, 5.9a, Vol. 9.c, 1989 May - Oct. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 6 No. 6, 9, 10, 12, 1990 June - Dec. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 7 No. 1 - 4, 1991 Jan. - Apr. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 7 No. 7, 8, 1991 Aug. - Nov. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Mouse Tracks [Portland OR] Vol. 8 No. 3, 1992 Mar. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Mousse's Tooth [Fairbanks AK] Vol. 1 No. 1 - 3, 5 - 7, 1982 Apr. - Dec. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Mousse's Tooth [Fairbanks AK] Vol. 2 No. 1 - 5, 1983 Feb. - Oct. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Mousse's Tooth [Fairbanks AK] Vol. 3 No. 7, 8, 1989 Nov. - Dec. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Mousse's Tooth [Fairbanks AK] Vol. 4 No. 1 - 4, 6 - 9, 1985 Jan. - Dec. (Box 37, Folder 7)